爱死这柠檬味了 太美妙
I like the lemon. So good.
配上香草糖霜
And with the vanilla frosting,
就是人见人爱的婚丧喜庆必备小蛋糕
It would make a lovely cupcake wedding cake.
天啊天啊天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
这巧克力
The chocolate!
-你知道你旁边还有别人吧 -我知道啊
- You do realize you're not alone, right? - I know.
我去喝两口水
I'm gonna get some water,
然后就回来继续试所有小蛋糕
and then I'll be back to taste everything!
她才没要结婚呢
There's no wedding.
-什么 -她是来骗蛋糕吃的
- What? - It's a scam.
她这套路老娘清楚
I know her game.
东海岸各地所有丹尼斯连锁餐厅
There isn't a Denny's on the eastern seaboard
姐全都去假装过当天是我生日
I haven't hit up and said it's my birthday
就为了吃免费圣代
for a free sundae.
那要是你误会人家
Well, what if you're wrong,
她真要结婚呢
and she is the real deal?
承包一个婚礼的小蛋糕能赚不少钱呢
A cupcake wedding cake could be a lot of money.
再她又回来白吃蛋糕前
We have to crack her B.S.
我们得先戳穿这胡扯新娘才行
before she eats our cupcakes, and then us.
看姐的
Follow my lead.
接下来要试哪一个呢
Oh! What are we tasting now?
椰子味的
Coconut.
-你未婚夫姓啥名啥 -道格·富兰克林
- What's your fiance's name? - Doug Franklin.
-怎么认识的 -他是个消防员
- Where'd you meet? - He's a fireman.
他救过我的猫
He rescued my cat.
少同情了 这是保险广告桥段
No, aw. That's an insurance commmmercia.
婚礼要在哪举行
So where's the wedding?
海滩裸足婚礼
Barefoot on the beach.
这是卫生棉条广告桥段
That's a tampon commercial.
宝贝 你来啦
Ooh! Hi, baby!
麦克斯 你错了 人家在接吻呢
Max, you're wrong. They're kissing.
他要么是她请来的失业男演员
Nope, he's either an out-of-work actor she hired,
要么就是他嘴里有蛋糕
or he has cake in his mouth.
我有一件事情要宣布
I have an announcement to make.
你"下面"终于长出第一根毛了吗
You found your first "down there" Hair?
不 现在是你们最后放入名片抽奖
No, it's the last chance to put in your business card
得到豪华周末游的机会
to win a luxury weekend vacation.
是阿憨大抽奖[高调基佬]
It's Han's big promo.
他终于正式宣布了
Well, he's finally announced it.
阿憨是个大基佬
Han's a big promo.
他只能算个小基基吧
Well, he's a little promo.
祝好运啦 你们现在
Good luck, you now have a chance
有机会赢到豪华乡间两室一厅套房
to win a fancy two-room suite in the country,
而且内有壁炉哦 因为小爷特大方
and there's a fireplace because daddy don't skimp.
我好想念我家乡间屋子的壁炉
Aw, I miss our fireplace in the country.
我都会跟老爸坐在壁炉前
My father and I would sit together,
我烤着棉花糖吃 而他会烧...
and I'd roast marshmallows, and then he'd burn
我现在才意识到他以前是在烧文件
what I now realize must've been incriminating documents.
各位好 抽奖女郎到啦
Hi, everybody! The raffle girl is here.
赢家的名片由我翻出呢
Oh, I get to pull the winner!
她今天就翻了我两次"牌"呢
She pulled me twice today,
两次我都"大获全胜"
and I won both times.
苏菲 你今晚的美貌
Sophie, the way you look tonight,
让我们都成为赢家
we are all winners.
厄尔 你嘴真甜
Oh, Earl, that is so sweet.
合法的话 我一定亲死你
I would kiss you if it was legal.
我也要放一张我清洁公司的名片进去
All right, I'm going to put in one of my cleaning company cards.
好啦
All right.
赢家会是谁呢
Who's gonna be the winner?
像甩宝丽来照片一样甩动身躯吧 宝贝
Yeah, yeah, shake it like a polaroid picture, baby.
好的
Yeah.
惨了 这张感觉不像是我的名片
Oh, no, that doesn't feel like my card.
苏菲 你这是作弊
Sophie, that's cheating.
好贱货格林达 你少管闲事
Hey, keep out of it, Glinda the good bitch.
赢家就是...
And the winner is...
麦克斯自制小蛋糕
Max's homemade cupcakes?
我的天啊 我们赢了
Oh, my God! We won!
恭喜你们
Congratulations!
我这辈子从来没赢过任何比赛呢
I've never won anything in my life!
除了有一次我吸毒昏头
Except for that time I got stoned
意外赢了一个热狗大胃王比赛
and accidentally won that hot dog eating contest.
等等 这怎么可能
Wait, how did this even happen?
你有丢我们的名片进去吗
Did you put our card in?
其实是我放入你们名片的
Actually, I put your card in,
而且我还抽了几张起来
and I took a few out.
我觉得你们俩姑娘应该去放个假
I figured you girls could use a vacation.
我发薪日大鱼大肉加烟酒 肝都是没你们累
You girls been working harder than my liver on payday.
厄尔 你简直就是圣诞老人啊
Oh, Earl, you're like Santa
除了你没恋童癖 其他都像
without the weird fixation on children.
厄尔帮我们参加投票真是太好心了
It was so nice of Earl to enter us.
别动歪脑筋 我当他是我爸呢
Oh, stop. He's like my father.
哇 这地方看起来还真不错呢
Wow, this place actually looks nice.
哇 有茅厕呢
Ooh, an outhouse!
麦克斯 那是桑拿房
Max, that's a sauna. Oh.
随便啦 我就要尿在里面
Either way, I'm peeing in it.
麦克斯 我们如何丢下小店啊
But Max, can we leave the shop?
虽然生意不是太好
I mean, even though business has been slow,
但要是多蒂回来
what if Dottie wants to come back
想要下她婚礼的小蛋糕订单怎么办
and order cupcakes for her wedding?
首先 早被她吃光了
First off, she ate them all.
其次 她也没要结婚
Second, there is no wedding.
她就是个胡扯新娘
She's a B.S. Bride.
我跟你保证 她现在
I guarantee you, right now,
肯定是在爬连锁甜甜圈店的空调管道
she's crawling through an air-conditioning vent
想潜进去偷吃呢
at a Krispy Kreme.
安迪驾到
Andy in the house!
抱歉 来之前看了好久的情景喜剧
Sorry, I was watching a Living Single marathon
一时难以自拔
before I came over.
说出来你肯定不相信
You are not gonna believe this.
我们赢了周末度假游呢
We won a weekend getaway.
超爽的对吧 我们太需要去度假了
Isn't that exciting? We really needed this.
太好啦
That's great!
我们的确需要这个 谢啦 宝贝
We do need this. Thanks, babe.
我本来也在计划要跟你共度一个
And I was hoping to get a little special
只属于我们俩人的周末呢
one-on-one time with you this weekend.
我们什么时候出发
So when do we leave?
我们
Oh, we!
我们可以明天出发
We can leave tomorrow.
我们 我们 我们一起去
We--we--we all the way there.
阿憨说那是一个两室一厅套房
Look, Han said it was a two-room suite.
安迪可以一起来的
Andy can come with us.
这旅行还是只属于我们
It's still our trip.
不必让他知道他是电灯泡的事实
He doesn't have to know he's the third wheel.
你知道我最爱骗人了
Well, you know I'm always a fan of lying,
当然没问题
So I'm in.
这旅行还是只属于我们
It's still our trip.
不必让她知道她是电灯泡的事实
She doesn't have to know she's the third wheel.
你知道我最不爱骗人了
Well, you know I'm not a fan of lying,
但还是没问题啦
But okay, I'm in.
我最爱开车旅行了
I love a road trip.
我三年级的时候跟我妈开车旅行了一年呢
My mom and I took one in third grade for, like, a year,
但我们就只是开车在当地转悠...
but we'd just drive around locally and--
靠 那年我们只是住车里
Oh, my God, I lived in a car.
来玩小游戏嘛
Hey, let's play a card game.
猜猜我看到了什么红色东西
I spy something red.
是那个加油站吗
Is it that gas station?
不是
Nope.
-是那台卡车吗 -不是
- Is it that truck? - Nope.
是"无聊"吗 是的 换我出题
Is it boring? Yes! My turn.
猜猜我看到了什么烦人东西
I spy something annoying.
-是我吗 -没错
- Is it me? - Yes!
我就知道你是在损我
I knew the joke was on me,
但我就是想赢
but I love to win.
你才不烦人呢 你可爱死了
You are not annoying. You're adorable.
猜猜我看见了什么娘炮东西
I spy a big man-gina.
-是我咩 -没错
- Is it me? - Yes!
我这人也爱赢
Like to win too.
麦克斯自制小蛋糕
Max's homemade cupcakes.
您好
Hello?
这附近没信号
Bad cell area.
麦克斯 可能是多蒂打来呢 胡扯新娘
Max, I think that might've been Dottie, the B.S. Bride.
我听不见她说什么
I couldn't hear the words,
但语气中有很不然的自信呢
but she sounded unnaturally confident.
人家可能不是胡扯 是胡买呢
Maybe the B.S. stands for "Big sale."
别再接公事电话了 好吗
No more business calls, okay?
我们来度假不是为了放松吗
I thought we were getting away for fun.
是啊 但我们的生意
We are, but our business
离我们预期目标差了十万八千里
is nowhere near where we need it to be,
所以就这么不理一通生意电话
and when it comes to ignoring a call,
真的有点难呢
it's kind of hard.
你们知道这一带山区最出名的是什么吗
Hey, you know what this area of the mountains is known for?
酒庄与乱伦吗
Wineries and incest?
是外星人绑架啦
Alien abductions!
我超了解这方面呢
I know all about it.
无数人都在这片山区中人间蒸发
People disappear from here all the time.
麦克斯 "天外来客"只是无稽之谈
Max, there's no such thing as an extraterrestrial.
真正的"天外来客"就会这么说
Okay, first, that's something an extraterrestrial would say.
我一直梦想有天被外星人绑架
I've always wanted to be abducted.
我的咨询顾问居然还骂我这人没目标
And my guidance counselor said I had no goals.
就是这间啦
And here we go.
哥认为名号只是云烟
Again, I don't believe in names,
但不叫不行的话 就叫我罗杰吧
but feel free to call me "Roger" if it helps you.
哇靠 哇靠
Yeah! Get out! Get out!
床是悬空的呢 太酷了
The bed floats! This is awesome!
通常玩捆绑得自己带绳子上床
Usually, you gotta bring the ropes to the bed.
它这样 让我们整整省了一大步骤呢
This way, you get to eliminate a whole step!
这床的雕工之美
The bed's sculptural beauty
常被休息于其中的舒适所盖过
is actually surpassed by the joy of resting in it.
有人赞 这就像是在神的怀抱之中
Some say it's like being rocked to sleep
摇摆入眠
in the arms of god.
就是张性爱床嘛 罗杰
It's a sex bed, Roger.
能让我替你们升火吗
May I light the fire for you?
不用 多谢 这我能搞定
Oh, no, thanks. I can do it.
我以前是鹰童军[最高级别童军]
I was an eagle scout.
这件牛事实在是没有太多机会
Man, there's just not enough occasions
能让我说出来显摆啊
where I can brag about at.
房间很有爱 就是有点小
The room is cute, but really tiny.
我们需要大一点的空间呢
We're gonna need a bigger space,
毕竟我们不是哈比人
unless we're hobbits.
这门是通往相邻房的吗
Is this the door to the adjoining room?
那的确通往相邻房
Well, that is an adjoining room,
但那房间并不包含在你们的套餐里
but it's not included in your package.
我靠
Oh, damn it!
我们早该想到阿憨说的
We should've known Han's package
绝对比实际的来的"小"
was gonna be smaller than he said it is.
很抱歉 其他小屋也都被订了
I'm sorry. All the other cabins are booked.
我去给你们多拿点睡沙发的寝具
I'll bring you some bedding for the couch
这要额外加钱哦
at an additional price.
大家平安[印度祈文]
Ohm shanti.
好吧 你们才是一对
Well, I guess you guys are the couple,
我去睡沙发吧
so I'll sleep on the couch.
我睡哪都行的
I can sleep anywhere.
我刚出生那两年
First two years of my life,
就是睡在一大叠没读过的信上呢
my bed was a pile of unopened mail.
烧得旺盛的炉火
A big, roaring fire
肯定会超级浪漫呢
is gonna be so romantic.
过来跟我靠近一点嘛
Come over here closer to me,
牛逼鹰童军哥哥
you big eagle scout.
你这语气好像我的童军团长
Well, now you sound like my scoutmaster.
不够时间"处理"好 就被乱"开始""啊
Hey, don't start anything you can't finish in a minute.
麦克斯很快会回来
Max'll be right out.
不知为何 就感觉她不是好好洗手的那种人
Something tells me she's not a consistent Hand-washer.
你忙你的吧
You do your thing.
我就在一边坐好
I'm just gonna sit right here,
然后看我男人升火
and watch my man build a fire.
这是雪松木呢
Oh, great, this is cedar!
烧起来味道很棒
It's gonna smell so awesome.
我最爱听着柴火燃烧的声音入眠了
I love falling asleep to the sound of a fire.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我知道不该忙公事
I know, no business stuff,
但有人发短信给我要下大单呢
but I just got a text about a big order.
没事 别忘了这个周末
That's fine, just remember this weekend--
我知道 我与你
Oh, I know, me and you.
我与你 我与你嘛
Me and you, me and you--
麦克斯 麦克斯
Max! Max.
原来胡扯新娘没胡扯呢
Turns out the B.S. bride isn't B.S.
她来问我们婚礼小蛋糕
She wants pricing on a wedding cupcake cake,
与新郎的小蛋糕蛋糕了 要供300位宾客呢
and a groom's cupcake cake, for 300 guests.
不错
Great!
但还比不上这毛绒小鞋鞋呢
Almost as great as these little fuzzy shoes!
它们被密封在塑料包装里
They were in a sealed plastic package.
而我是第一个拆封的人
I'm the first one to ever open them.
简直就像是给脚穿的避孕套呢
They're like condoms for your feet!
新鞋鞋 新鞋鞋
New shoes, new shoes
你上哪呢
Where are you going?
去桑拿房啊
To the sauna.
真希望可以在路上被外星人绑架
Hopefully, I'll be abducted on my way,
我希望你们知道 就算被绑架
but know that even though I'm gone,
我也会跟我的外星爱人过更幸福的日子
I'm happier up there with my alien lover.
的确 它们没有嘴唇
True, they don't have lips,
但它们有超长的手指可以"服务"我啊
but they do have crazy-long fingers.
我跟你一起去吧
I'll go with you.
不是去谈公事
Not to talk about work,
但总不能让她自己去 附近可能有熊呢
but she can't go alone. There might be bears.
我在瑞士的山中小屋附近就老有熊
There were always bears at my chalet in Aspen,
在林子里啊 躺地上啊 到处都有熊
in the woods, lying on the floors, everywhere.
善待动物组织来过之后 才全没有的
You know, until PETA attacked the house.
这就是传输中的桑拿房啊
So this is a fancy sauna?
真不咋地
Not impressed.
居然有人愿意花钱
People pay for the privilege
来坐在别人留下的无数屁股汗上
of sitting in decades of ass sweat?
为什么你的毛巾
How come your towel's staying up
比我的紧那么多
so much better than mine?
我能想到"两个"理由
I can think of two reasons.
我要去喝点水 好回来开尿了
I'm gonna get some water, and then start peeing.
等你回来 我们还得谈谈
When you come back, we have to discuss
胡扯新娘小蛋糕一事
the B.S. Bride's cake.
这单子不能搞砸啊 就靠这单了
We can't screw this up. It's all we have.
这蒸得太爽了
This heat is amazing.
亲娘地 真烫啊
Mother of God! That's hot.
外面有熊呢
There are bears out there.
-朝这里过来了 -什么
- They're coming this way. - What?
麦克斯 快躲进来 关上门啊
Max, get in here! Close the door!
随便 他们照样会开门进来
Fine, but they'll just open it and come in.
熊才没办法开门走进来呢
Bears can't open doors and walk in.
这种熊就可以
These ones can.
-好啊 -姑娘们好
- Oh, hi. - Hey, girls.
不介意我们一起蒸吧
You mind if we join you?
你们俩是基熊男 对吧
You guys are gay bears, right?
-麦克斯 -没事的
- Max! - It's cool.
我当年舞会的伴现在是熊界一霸呢
My prom date is big in the bear scene now,
但当年我们高中时 大家都叫他
but in high school, they just called him a jock
爱哭的大汉
who cried sometimes.
我们就是熊男 魁梧 毛多 但温顺哦
Yep, we're bears. Big, hairy, not scary.
我是迪克[音似阴茎] 我是德克[短剑]
I'm Deke. This is Dirk.
我们就是"阴剑"双侠
Yup, we're Deke and Dirk.
暂停等你们作反应
Pause for reaction.
我是卡洛琳 她是麦克斯
I'm Caroline, and this is Max.
你们是唇膏女同吗[十分女性化的女同]
Are you girls lipstick lesbians?
不是 单纯朋友而已
No, we're just friends,
而且我们也买不起唇膏
And we can't afford lipstick.
在他这礼品店就更买不起了
Especially at this gift shop.
你们看到东西标价了吗
Have you seen the prices?
25块钱买管护唇膏
$25 for chap stick?
谁嘴唇烂到要这么贵的东西护啊
Please. No one's lips are that chapped.
他很懂这方面
And he would know.
他可是面霜[颜射]之王呢
This one's the king of face creaming.
比那个还肮脏一点哦
A little bit dirtier than what it is.
其实我是皮肤科医生啦
I'm actually a dermatologist.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我不会是有这种天大荣幸
Do not tell me I'm lucky enough
可以跟两位皮肤科医生共蒸桑拿吧
to be in a sauna with two dermatologists.
不不不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
我是个天体物理学家
I'm an astrophysicist.
哇 比普通熊男更才高八斗呢
Oh, smarter than the average bear.
爱死她了
Loving her.
那想必你很懂太空事物啦 聪明熊
So you know about space stuff, smarty bear.
你相信外星人的存在吗
Do you believe in aliens?
当然 而且我相信它们就活在我们之中
Oh, I do, and I believe they're living among us.
就是说你呢 克里斯蒂娜·里奇
I'm looking at you, Christina Ricci!
迪克 你说吧 你哪有什么货能给我啊
So talk to me, Deke. What can you give me?
他有带一堆面霜试用品来呢
He has plenty of free cream samples
就在我们房里呢
back in our room.
而且都是好货哦 记得来拿
And it's the good stuff. You should come by!
我们就住四号小屋
We're in cabin four.
不是吧 我们住三号小屋呢
No way! We're in cabin three.
那个绳索吊床如何啊
How about those rope beds?
一看床被"捆绑"好 就知道要"色色"的了
You know it's kinky when the bed is already tied up.
一开始 我们俩说 "会摔吧"
First, we were all "um, we're gonna fall,"
但转念一想 "摔就摔吧"
but then we thought, "what the hell?
这是我们的基婚纪念日
It's our man-iversary."
你们结婚啦
Aw, you're married?
纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary.
再来谈谈那免费面霜吧
Now, let's get back to those free creams.
对了 这是我们名片
Oh, and here's our card
哪天你们刚好来到附近
if you're ever in the neighborhood
或有大单子就来吧
or need a big order.
你蒸个桑拿都带名片来啊
You brought a business card to a sauna?
我不想知道你怎么"夹"带进来的
I don't wanna know where you kept that.
麦克斯自制小蛋糕
Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
或者说是 小熊蛋糕
Or in your case, cub-cakes.
-爱死她 -爆喜欢她
- Loving her. - Living for her.
都想下辈子投胎变成她了
Wanna come back as her.
这是你们的"二人"晚餐
There you go, your dinner for two.
两份汤 两份沙拉 两份主菜 两份甜点
Two soups, two salads, two entrees, two desserts.
希望你们"三个"能吃得愉快
I hope you three enjoy.
我们能不能再点一份呢
Maybe could we order another meal?
没问题 打服务电话就行
No problem, just call.
当然 要额外收费哦
Extra charge, of course.
大家平安
Ohm Shanti.
其实是瑜伽里"坑爹"的意思 对吧
Ohm Shanti means "screw you" in yoga, right?
我要饿死了
I am so starving.
天啊 看起来真好吃
Oh, my God, this looks amazing!
面包还是温的呢
Oh, and the bread is still warm!
还有一个超怪异的椒盐脆饼卷
And there's one of those crazy-ass pretzel rolls.
到底是脆饼 还是面包卷
Is it a pretzel? Is it a roll?
不晓得 反正就是超怪
No idea, it's crazy.
麦克斯 涂点这些奶油上去
Max, put some of this butter on it.
想让我不涂都不行 贱人
Try and stop me, bitch!
-来 一人一半 -谢谢
- Here, take half. - Thanks!
吃得开心吗
Yo.
天啊 安迪 我完全忘了
Oh, my God, Andy! I totally forgot.
不是忘了你的存在 而是忘了我的礼貌
Not about you. I forgot my manners.
如果我的丹麦家庭老师在这里
If my Danish governess were here,
她一定会拿她的木勺子打我的
she would hit me with her wooden spoon.
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
来 坐下 你吃
Go, sit. You eat.
好好享受椒盐脆饼卷
Enjoy the pretzel roll.
没了 先下手为强 后下手遭殃
It's gone. You snooze, you lose.
不 你坐吧 我无所谓
No, you sit. I'm good.
我再点多点吃的
I'll order more food.
不 你坐 你坐
No, sit! Sit.
我才是坏人
I'm the bad one.
这汤"强赞"啊
This soup is "Duh-mazing."
这词是我瞎编的
Just a word I made up
当有事物赞得吓着你时
for when something's so amazing, you're stunned,
你只能用一个字来形容 "强"
and all you can say is "Duh."
强赞
Duh-mazing.
对 我想再点一份...
Yes, I'd like to order anoth--
好的 我等着
Yes, I'll hold.
我觉得等待音乐是罗杰在唱歌
I think the hold music is just Roger singing.
好啦 把电话放下
Okay, hang up the phone.
去坐下吃吧 来啦
Go sit and eat. Come on.
快点 不然麦克斯连桌子都要吃掉了
Hurry before Max eats the table.
不 你吃
No, you eat.
毕竟这是我们的专属周末
After all, it's our special weekend.
我想让你过得开心
I want you to enjoy it.
好吧
Well, okay,
但只因为这次情节特殊
but only because it's a special occasion.
很好
Good!
我去洗个热水澡
I'm gonna go take a hot shower.
再说了 向来空腹做爱感觉更棒
Besides, it's always better to make love on an empty stomach.
怪不得闹饥荒的印度 人会这么多了
That must be why there are so many people in India.
麦克斯 我有一事相求
Max, I got a favor to ask you.
你能不能给我们俩一点独处时间
Do you think you can go visit your bear friends next door,
去隔壁基熊朋友那里待会
maybe give us some private time?
就当是你送我的生日礼物
It'll be your birthday gift to me.
当是我送给你的生日礼物
It would be my birthday gift to you
所以是你过生日咯
because it's your birthday.
对啊 两个小时就好
Yeah, just for, like, two hours.
好吧 一小时也行
Okay, one hour.
我略过前戏好了
I'll skip the foreplay,
那就当是我送给自己的生日礼物吧
and that'll be my birthday gift to myself.
好的 那我这就过去
Cool, then I'll just go do that, then.
我猜卡洛琳费了那么大的劲
I mean, Caroline went to all this trouble
这次旅行就是想给你庆祝生日吧
to get you a trip for your birthday, I assume.
我知道
I know,
我一直期待会有特别的生日爱爱
and I was really looking forward to some birthday sex
因为自从蛋糕店生意不顺之后
since we haven't really connected that way
我们也情路不顺 没滚过床单了
since the shop started giving you guys so much trouble.
但是蛋糕店已经不顺好几周啦
But the shop's been in trouble for weeks.
是啊 或许时间可以缩短到半个小时
Yeah, so maybe I'll only need, like, a half hour with her.
我要拿上书 我要泡个澡
I need my book. I'm gonna take a bath instead.
浴缸太棒了
That tub is so amazing.
我要在泡在里面
I'm just gonna soak in it
幸福到忘掉我所有的难题
and blissfully forget all my problems.
忘掉的还有别的事情哦
As well as some other things.
麦克斯打算去隔壁拜访瑜伽熊和波波熊
Max is gonna go visit Yogi and Boo Boo next door
好让我们过下二人世界
and give us some private time.
她不能这么做
She can't do that.
今天可是他们的"基年纪念日"
It's their man-iversary.
他们也需要二人世界
They need their private time.
话是没错 但是你们俩
Yes, but you guys
也有事情要庆祝哦
are celebrating a special thing, too.
什么 我们要庆祝什么吗
What? What are we celebrating?
安迪的生日啊 讨厌
Andy's birthday. Oh, damn it!
我不小心破坏了你精心为他准备的
Now, I went and spoiled all the special sexual things
特别爱爱惊喜
you had planned for him.
就是 麦克斯
Damn it, Max!
现在被你弄得惊喜全无了
Now, you did give it all away.
我们本来要玩传教士式的
We were gonna do missionary,
以及...
and...
另外一种招式
...the other one.
好啦
Okay.
好啦 对不起 我忘记了
Okay, I'm sorry. I forgot.
我不知怎么忘了 我明明早知道你今天生日
I don't know how. I knew today was your birthday.
是明天
It's tomorrow.
太好了
So yippee!
那她还没有错过
She hasn't missed it.
世间一切太平
All's right with the world.
我要去找熊夫夫玩了
I'm gonna go visit the berenstains.
这个周末不是特意为我庆祝生日的 对吧
This weekend wasn't about my birthday, was it?
快开门 快开门
Come on, come on.
把手从他的"蜜罐"里拿开
Get your hand out of his honeypot
快过来给老娘开门
and get over here.
我马上就走
I'll be gone in a second,
然后你们俩就可以再续你们的性爱生活啦
and then you guys can jump-start your sex life again.
为什么会说"再续"
What do you mean "Jump-start"?
你怎么能告诉麦克斯 我们很久没做了呢
How could you tell Max that we haven't had sex?
你都没跟我本人讨论过呢
You haven't even discussed that with me.
快开门啊 外星人
Come on, aliens.
如果你真想绑架我
If you're ever going to abduct me,
现在就是最好的时机
this would be the time.
别转移你忘记我生日的
Don't take the attention off the fact
这一事实
that you forgot my birthday.
天啊 我真希望我是卡通人物
Oh, God, I wish I was a cartoon,
这样我就可以直接穿过这扇门
so I could run right through this door,
然后留下一个身形的门洞
and leave behind a body-shaped hole.
麦克斯
Oh, hey, Max.
介意我进来"避寒"一下吗
Mind if I hibernate for a minute?
当然不介意 快进来
Oh, sure, come on in.
我们刚准备吃饭 然后染我们的胸毛
We were just gonna eat and then dye our chest hair.
快把这扇该死的门关上
Close that damn door now.
谢谢 那边的气氛刚才有点紧张
Thanks, it was just getting a little tense in there.
-她忘记了他的生日 -真伤心
- She forgot his birthday. - Mm, ouch.
他有次也忘记了我的生日
Well, he forgot mine once,
就被罚纹我生日在脚踝了
and now it's his ankle tattoo.
麦克斯 来 快请坐
Max, please, I insist.
我很随和 不必多问
You don't have to ask me twice.
你们要吃椒盐脆饼吗
You gonna eat the pretzel roll?
安迪 抱歉忘了你的生日
Andy, I'm sorry about your birthday.
我脑子愣是没记住
It just went out of my head.
我很内疚
I feel bad.
我很想吐
And I feel sick.
你能不能别晃这张床了
Can you stop swinging the bed?
抱歉 我紧张嘛
Sorry, I'm nervous.
对啊 你就是常常紧张
Yeah, you're nervous a lot,
所以我们其他的床从来不"动"
which is why our other bed isn't moving at all.
别别别 别走啊
No, no, no, no, no, don't go.
过来 快回到性爱之床上
Come back. Come back to the sex bed.
我们现在就开"动"吧
Let's get some sex going!
来啊 我们现在就能让这床"大动特动"
Come on! We can get this bed moving now!
看
See!
看见没
See?
今天是你的生日 今天是你的生日
Oh, it's your birthday! It's your birthday!
是明天啦
It's tomorrow.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
我可以做得更好 你看
I can do better, see?
好戏上场
Here we go!
精彩不断
Now, here we go!
想看我跳钢管舞吗
Wanna see me twerk it?
如果我有吃东西 一定全吐出来
If I'd had any food, I would throw up.
好了 快坐下来吧
Okay, yeah, have a seat.
吃点面包
Let's have some bread.
我们真的有那么久没做爱了吗
Has it really been that long since we had sex?
亲爱的 跳完那段舞
Sweetie, after that dance,
很难相信会有人愿意跟你做爱
it's hard to believe you've ever had sex.
没有那么久啦
It hasn't been that long.
蛋糕店是12号开业的
The shop opened on the 12th,
所以...
so it's...
怎么了
What?
没什么 真有意思
No, it's just interesting
开业的日子你倒是能轻易想起来
you had no problem remembering that date.
那我问你个问题
Let me ask you a question.
你觉得你会走到哪里
Where do you think you're going?
这话什么意思 我就在这里啊
What do you mean? I'm here.
不
No.
你觉得你以后的路会走到哪里
Where do you think you're going?
比如 你觉得你一年后的生活会如何
Like, where do you see your life in a year?
很快 我和麦克斯
Well, pretty soon, Max and I
将会度过这个难关
will be out of this rough patch,
并全力以赴经营蛋糕店
and full force with the business,
承办婚礼和大型宴会
doing weddings and big events,
然后我和麦克斯可能会开一家分店
and then Max and I will probably open another store,
换一间大点的公寓
get a bigger apartment.
好 那这里面有我吗
Okay, and am I in there somewhere?
拜托 我刚准备说你呢
Oh, come on. I was getting to you.
是吗
Were you?
什么时候 什么时候才会轮到我
When? When were you getting to me?
在你的事业获得成功之后吗
After your business is a success?
不 现在啊
No! Now.
来嘛 在性爱之床上滚床单
Come on. Sex time in the sex bed.
想在地板上"滚"吗
Wanna do it on the floor?
这真是太舒服了
This is so comfortable!
系个腰带 都可以直接穿出门了
You put a belt on this, you could wear it out.
千万不要在你亲家的房子这么穿
Just don't try that at your in-laws' house
还配上成套的头巾
with a matching turban.
德克 我父亲在失去一只手臂前
Dirk, my father worked 40 years in the factory
在满是男子汉的工厂里干了40年
before he lost his arm.
-他接受不了娘炮男同 -好吧
- He doesn't get "Camp." - Okay.
快上来 小姑娘
Now get up here, lady.
我们要吃饼干喝牛奶了
We're having cookies and milk.
你们俩太棒了
You guys rock.
我保证不会整晚待在这里的
I promise I won't stay here all night.
我可不想妨碍你们的
Don't wanna get trapped in the middle
乡间"熊熊狂欢夜"时光
of your country bear jamboree.
拜托 亲爱的
Please, honey.
你在这张床上很安全
You are perfectly safe in this bed.
我们一年没做过爱了
We haven't had sex in a year.
你干嘛告诉她那个
Why would you tell her that?
她告诉我们 她的朋友很久没做啦
Well, she told us about her friends not having sex.
我以为这种事可以公开说啊
I thought it was on the table.
但这件事甚至连我们自己都没谈过
But we haven't even discussed that.
外星母舰 让我梦想成真吧
Mother ship, make it happen!
此时不绑更待何时啊
This is the time to abduct me.
麦克斯 你可以回来了 安迪走了
Hi. Max, you can come back. Andy left.
他说他会想办法回家的
He said he'd find his own way home.
-他走了 -就因为你们不做爱吗
- He left? - Because you're not having sex?
麦克斯 你居然告诉这对基熊我们不做爱
Max, you told the bears we're not having sex?
你干嘛要分享这种事
Why would you share that?
就是 卡洛琳
Exactly, Caroline.
为什么你要告诉麦克斯
And why would you tell Max that,
而在我们做格式塔疗时却绝口不提呢
when you never even brought it up in our Gestalt therapy?
我本打算这周末正式跟你说的
I was planning on addressing it with you this weekend.
不然你觉得我花500大洋开这间房
You think I'd spend $500 on this room
就为了喝牛奶吃饼干吗
for milk and cookies?
我觉得我们都忘了
I think we're all forgetting
汤的味道有多棒
how good that soup was.
抱歉我最近觉得自己不太有魅力
Well, I'm sorry if I haven't been feeling very attractive lately.
我可是每天都告诉你 你有多帅哦
I tell you how handsome you are every day.
你们俩不是长得很像吗
Don't you guys look exactly alike?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
I'm all right.
你想上床大家抱抱一下吗
You wanna get in bed and cuddle for a little while?
不用了...好吧
No, it's-- yeah.
-来啦 -对啊 来这里
- Come on. - Yeah, get in here.
这才对嘛
There you go. There you go.
太好了 你还活着
Oh, good. You're alive.
当我听说你离开 独自穿过树林时
When I heard you left and walked through the woods,
我心想 "会不会被抓去肛门探测"
I wondered, "was there anal probing?"
被外星人"探测" 而不是被骗子骗
By an alien, not a grifter.
是你发短信说想见我吗
You texted you wanted to see me?
是某人啦
Well, someone did.
生日快乐
Happy Birthday!
来 快吹[吹箫]
Now, come on, blow.
我不是很想做这事
I don't really feel like doing that.
欢迎来到女人的世界
Welcome to our world.
安迪 我为发生的一切感到抱歉
Andy, I'm so sorry about everything.
没关系
It's okay.
我坐公车的时候 有很多时间思考
I had a lot of time to think on the bus,
因为我要转车 然后转的车坏了
and the other bus, and the bus I had to take
我又得再转一辆车
when that bus broke down.
如果能让你感觉好点
If it makes you feel any better,
我的后背全是绳子擦伤的痕迹呢
I have rope burns all down my back.
安迪 抱歉忘了你的生日
Andy, I'm sorry about your birthday.
我们是一个月前告诉彼此对方生日的
We told each other those dates a month ago.
我都不指望你会记得我的
I wouldn't expect you to remember mine.
1987年5月28日
May 28th, 1987.
早上10点30分
10:30 in the morning.
是晚上10点30分 所以你也不完美嘛
10:30 at night, so you're not perfect.
你的人生很忙
Look, you have a really busy life,
你也很要强 这点我很敬佩
and you're really ambitious, which I admire,
但我不想做一个要等着你人生里有我的人
but I wanna be more than someone you get to eventually.
当然不是这样
And you deserve that.
只不过我现在要以事业为先...
It's just I have to put the business first right now--
我明白
And I get that.
我觉得我们该冷静一下
I just--I think we should take a break.
你想冷静一下
You wanna take a break?
或许 是吧
Maybe, yeah.
你真正想说的是不是"分手"
Are you saying take a break
"冷静一下"不过是
'cause you really mean "Break up,"
你不忍心才这么说
but you're trying to be nice?
或许 是吧
Maybe, yeah.
抱歉这一切来得这么突然
I'm sorry if this seems sudden,
但我了解自己
but I know me,
或许长痛不如短痛
and maybe it's better sooner than later.
我回来啦
I'm back!
我还把我的伴娘都带来了
And I brought my bridesmaids!
看起来生意在好转嘛
Looks like business is picking up.
要不见你 会很难吧
It's gonna be hard not to see you.
是啊 的确
Yeah, it will be.
我就在你10英尺外工作
I work 10 feet away.
这边 姑娘们
This way, ladies.
我们要尝遍她们所有的小蛋糕
We're gonna taste every cupcake they have!
现在是带我走的最佳时机
This is the time to take me!
快点 最后一次求你了
Come on, final offer!
ET 阿福[电视剧外星人]
E.T.? Alf?
克里斯蒂娜·里奇
Christina Ricci?